Quynh Da Le, Frontend Developer

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam, 0865781317, daquynh2403@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn

SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated and dedicated front-end developer with a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science and 2 years of professional experience. Known for my attention to detail, creativity, and problem-solving abilities, I strive to create visually stunning and user-friendly web applications.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Java

Frameworks/Technologies:

- Javascript: Reactjs, Vuejs, Nuxtjs, Nodejs, Redux
- HTML5 & CSS3: Bootstrap, TailwindCss, Sass
- Java: SpringMVC, Hibernate, SpringBoot

Database Management Systems: MySQL, MongoDB

Languages: Vietnamese, English (IELTS 6.5)

Others:

- Understanding of OOP methodologies, SOLID principles, and design patterns.
- Experienced with AWS Cloud Computing Platform, CI/CD, Docker, and Kubernetes.
- Familiar with GIT version control, and collaboration tools like Jira, Confluence
- Solid understanding of responsive design, cross-browser compatibility, performance optimization, debugging and testing

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

May 2023 — Present

Frontend Developer, I-ON Communications

Viet Nam

Project: I-ON Content Management System (CMS) (10 members)

- Description: I-ON CMS provides a comprehensive content management solution for businesses, enabling effective creation, organization, and publishing of content across multiple channels. The CMS offers features such as content authoring, workflow management, version control, and multi-language support.
- Technologies:
 - Frontend: Reactjs, Vuejs, Nuxtjs, Sass, AntDesign
 - Backend: Java
- · Responsibilities:
 - Translating UI/UX designs in Figma into functional and visually appealing web interfaces by creating the layout, styling, and interactive layers of the components.
 - Building reusable and modular components. Write clean and maintainable code that follows best
 practices, enabling other team members to easily reuse and extend these components across the
 landing pages.
 - Involve in interacting with backend services and APIs, and integrate these services into the frontend builders including: handling data retrieval, authentication, input validation, and data manipulation using RESTful APIs.

Jun 2022 — May 2023

Junior Software Engineer, Skedulo

Viet Nam

Project: Platform - Tooling (7 members)

• Description: Skedulo provides a cloud-based scheduling and management platform designed to help organizations manage their mobile workforces more efficiently and effectively. The tooling team provides and maintains services, highly supports internal users across tenants.

- Technologies:
 - Frontend: Reactjs, Typescript, TailwindCss, Jest, GraphQL
 - Backend: Nodejs, PostgreSQL
- Responsibilities:
 - Launched UI revamp of Packaging Import/Export by using Platform components.
 - Developed migration script for moving admin settings and custom-form across tenants by using Oclif, and JavaScript.
 - Support the CX team to deploy their product to AWS Lambda.
 - Roll Circle CI secrets for services.
 - · Changed and maintained source code to improve performance.

PROJECTS

Shopping webpage using MERN Stack

- Designed and built a gear-shopping service using MongoDB and NodeJS
- Implemented ReactJS and TailwindCSS to design and develop a UI webpage
- Presented flows in diagram form and documented the project

Shopping cart using OOP

- Designed and built a phone shopping cart using OOP methodologies and JSF (JavaServer Faces)
- Implemented Hibernate to simply interact between Java applications and databases.

EDUCATION

Sep 2018 — Dec 2022

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, HCMC Open University

Viet Nam